NARINTHORN NARIN

I'm ready to learn, have the patience and honesty.

A fast-learner, strong communication and fueled with a passion in Human Resources Management, Marketing and content creator. Offers expertise in HRM multi-function (except for recruitment process, training and labor relations), Administrative and Project management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MAGIC BOX DIGITAL CO., LTD. PROJECT COORDINATOR (LIVE STREAMING TEAM)

February 2021- July 2021 Bangkok, Thailand

- In charged of coordinating with 200 Creator Partner and Facebook Partner including follow-up Marketing project.
- Assist in coordinating marketing event and creator event.
- Prepared Creator reports such as performance weekly, overall monthly and support as assigned.
- Post-Live Streaming: Advice to creator able to engage an audience to watch live streaming, Assistant and prepare before live starts.
- Provide administrative support to live-streamers during their live shows with customer support and payments administration.
- Prepared job timing for creator through weekly schedule.
- Follow up with potential creator.
- Reconciliation and preparation of the delivery reports post live streaming.

BIODIVERSITY-BASED ECONOMY DEVELOPMENT OFFICE (PUBLIC ORGANIZATION) PROJECT COORDINATOR (CONTRACT WORK)

November 2020 – January 2021, Nonthaburi, Thailand

- In charged of coordinating with internal and external departments including follow-up Information of the digital project.
- · Assist in coordinating digital plans and digital risk management plan.
- Prepared reports such as correspondence work, procurement and support as assigned.

PROPERTY AND SPORTS MANAGEMENT OFFICE THAMMASAT UNIVERSITY (RUNGSIT) HR & ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

August 2016 – March 2020 Pathum Thani, Thailand

- In charged of preparing accounts and tax returns. Administering payrolls, controlling income and expenditure
- In charged of Carrying out administrative duties such as filing, typing, copying, binding, scanning etc.
- Direct phone calls and Provide information by answering questions and requests.
- Assist in the preparation of regularly scheduled reports.
- In charged of auditing financial information. Compiling and presenting reports, budgets, commentaries and financial statements.
- Direct phone calls and Provide information by answering questions and requests. Assist in the preparation of regularly scheduled reports.

THAMMASAT CONVENTION CENTER RECEPTIONIST (PARTTIME WORK)

August 2016 – March 2020 Pathum Thani, Thailand

- welcome and facilitate customers
- Maintain luggage storage system for lockers customer booking
- Provide information by answering questions, requests and advises to customers.
- Keeping the reception area in front of the center service and inside the meeting room always available.
- In charge of checking equipment and coordinate with the maintenance.
- In charge of regularly customer daily scheduled reports.

STUDY PROJECT

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1Dkf4iKBmGAqQyoH1RP0gem840SwajF4X?usp=sharing

- Conducted, designed and developed Training project "Growth your Leadership" (2019)
- Conducted a business plan for application for elderly person brand "O'Trainer" (2019)
- Research Proposal involved studying the influence of Thai LGBT movies showed during 2007-2017 toward the behavior of the students about human right issue. (2018)
- Analyzed strategy planning for Thai public management "Thailand Professional Qualification Institute (Public Organization)" (2017)



CONTACT ME AT:

A PHONE: 093 245 7288

EMAIL: NARINTR99@GMAIL.COM

HOUSE ADDRESS: 59/54 SOI
PETCHARAT 5 PRACHACHUENNONTHABURI 8 RD.,
BANGKHEN SUB DISTRICT,
MUEANG NONTHABURI
DISTRICT, NONTHABURI 11000

EDUCATION

THAMMASAT UNIVERSITY

Bachelor Degree of Political Science | Graduated May 2020 with a GPA of 3.19

- Major in Public Administration
- Minor in Organization, Entrepreneurship and Human Resources Management

PUA SCHOOL, NAN

high school of Science-Mathematics program | Graduated March 2016 with a GPAX of 3.45

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

Language

Thai (Native), Fair command of written, read and spoken English and beginner of Lao and Korean language.

- Computer Program
 - Typing skills: Thai, 45 words per minute and English, 50 words per minute
- proficient in Microsoft Office & Google Suite
 - excel, power point and word.
- Graphic Design
 - canva, figma
- Social Media Management
- Having Logical and analytical skills, highly responsible with strong problem solving.
- Strong interpersonal skills, Great collaboration, service mind
- leadership and working well in a team player
- Good in management presentation, time management and Public speaking skills

REFERENCES

MISS SIRADA SUKONTAPATIPARK

Human Resources Department, Magic Box DIGITAL Co., Ltd., Bangkok THAILAND

- Tel.092-2620962
- E-mail:sirada@magicboxasia.com

MR.TADTEP SAELIM

Head of Human Resources Department,
Property and Sports Management Office at
Thammasat University (Rungsit), Pathum Thani

- Tel.02-1510048
- E-mail:tadtep21@gmail.com